persistiq.com 2016-11-28

# PersistIQ

Last updated: October 22, 2014

We at CycleIO, Inc. (“PersistIQ,” “we,” “us,” “our”) know that our users (“you,” “your”) care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes how PersistIQ collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.PersistIQ.com

Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the Website or Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. Any capitalized terms used herein without definition shall have the meaning given to them in the PersistIQ Terms of Use.

## I. WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website or Services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined in our Terms of Use). No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services.

## II. WHAT INFORMATION DOES PersistIQ COLLECT?

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this Personal Information to personalize and improve the Services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for the Services, to analyze how users utilize the Website, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties (described in this Section and in Section IV below). We collect the following types of information:

### A. Information You Provide to Us:

Your Personal Information: We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, we collect Personal Information such as your name, email address, and browser information. You can choose not to provide us with certain information such as your credit card information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you cannot be individually identified, and provide that information to our partners.

Your Customers’ Personal Information: In order to provide you with the Services, we also receive and store any information you choose to provide us with respect to your customers (“Prospect” or “Prospects”). The Prospects information (“Prospects Information”) we receive and store typically includes names and email addresses of your customers, but will consist of any information you choose to provide us with.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. PersistIQ stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at support@persistiq.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

### B. Information Collected Automatically:

Whenever you interact with our Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our Website are visited by you. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our Website’s features. If you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

When you visit the Website, whether as a PersistIQ customer or a non-registered user just browsing, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). For example, Log Data may include information such as your computer’s IP address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Website and the Services and for the Website’s technical administration, to increase our Website’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors’ needs.

Additionally, as part of our provision of the Services to you, if you install certain software code provided by us on your website, we will also track and collect Prospect usage information on your website. We also use third parties to collect publicly available information relating to your Prospects. For more information on how we collect and compile Prospect Information, please see Section IV below.

The use of cookies by our tracking utilities is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our tracking utilities use both session ID and persistent cookies to enable us to design a better experience for our customers.

Our third party partners also employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do [not] tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personal information.

As you browse PersistIQ and other websites, online ad networks we work with may place anonymous cookies on your computer, and use similar technologies, in order to understand your interests based on your (anonymous) online activities, and thus to tailor more relevant ads to you. If you do not wish to receive such tailored advertising, you can visit this [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) to opt out of most companies that engage in such advertising. (This will not prevent you from seeing ads; the ads simply will not be delivered through these targeting methods.)

### C. E-mail and Other Communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may communicate with you about your use of the Website or Services. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by notifying us via email at support@persistiq.com or adjusting the settings on your account screen in the Website (where available). Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at support@persistiq.com.

## III. WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you are located outside the United States, the information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored and processed at, a destination in the United States. By submitting information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## IV. WILL PERSISTIQ SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information or your Prospects’ Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We share such Personal Information in personally identifiable form with third parties as described below.

A. Trusted Third Parties: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide the Services to you. Unless we tell you differently, such third parties do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. This includes third party companies and individuals employed by us to facilitate our Services, including the provision of maintenance services, database management, Web analytics and general improvement of the Services. In particular, as part of our provision of the Services to you, we provide a limited amount of your Prospect Information to Full Contact, Inc. (“Full Contact”) so that Full Contact can collect and compile publicly available contact and social information related to your Prospects, such as email addresses, gender, company, job titles, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses. For more information on the privacy practices of Full Contact, please visit http://fullcontact.com/privacy. You may opt-out of having such information sent to Full Contact by adjusting the settings on your app screen in the Website or notifying us by email at support@persistiq.com.

B. Business Transfers: We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

C. Protection of PersistIQ and Others: We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or a court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of PersistIQ, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

D. With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

## V. IS THE PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. The transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

When you enter your information on our site we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site’s privacy policy.

## VI. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you’ve provided to us:

name and password

email address

credit card information

The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Website changes. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at support@persistiq.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to: support@persistiq.com.

### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. To request removal of your personal information from Testimonials or comments please contact us at support@persistiq.com

## VII. WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?

You can always opt not to disclose information to use, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features. You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained in Section VI above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. You may request deletion of your account by contacting us at support@persistiq.com. Please note that some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@persistiq.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## VIII. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes or changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email prior to the change becoming effective. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted.

## IX. QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message support@persistiq.com We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

1501 Mariposa St, San Francisco, CA 94043
